Guide to the Collège de la Sainte Famille Collection AD.MC.028
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- A children's nursery on Thabet Street in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1957-1958 (Object AD_MC_028_ref312)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Kindergartens/Nurseries; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A Coptic - Evangelical church in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1901 (Object AD_MC_028_ref313)
  Photographic Prints; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Sites; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group school photo of teachers and clergymen. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref314)
  Head Covers/Veils; Men; Color Photography; Women; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Hats; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- Kiosk on Onsi Street in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1950 (Object AD_MC_028_ref315)
  Italian Writing; Kiosks/Kushk; Arabic Writing; Streets/Roads; Men; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Hats; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Holy Family Church. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1890 (Object AD_MC_028_ref316)
  Photographic Prints; Architecture; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Churches; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Religious Sites; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Ezbet El-Walda, tombs of first and second dynasties. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref317)
  Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Tombs/Mausoleums; Pottery; Arabic Writing; Cemeteries; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Religious Sites; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Monument to the Bonavia family in the Catholic cemetery in Helwan. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref318)
  Statues/Sculptures; Cemeteries; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Tombs/Mausoleums; Architecture; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Jewish Cemetery in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref319)
  Architecture; Photographic Prints; Religious Sites; Cemeteries; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints; Tombs/Mausoleums; Arabic Writing
- A view of a mosque, church and a school. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref320)
  Schools/Education; Religious Sites; Buildings; Churches; Mosques; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints
- The Japanese Garden. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1948-1949 (Object AD_MC_028_ref321)
  Parks; Water; Photographic Prints; Statues/Sculptures; Japanese Garden, Helwan, Egypt; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Facade of villa no. 11 on Mansour Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref322)
  Italian Writing; Streets/Roads; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Greek Orthodox Church on Sherif street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref323)
  Photographic Prints; Religious Crosses; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Arabic Writing; Religious Sites; Italian Writing; Orthodox Christianity; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Conversion of school building to a prison during the war in 1943 in Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm (Object AD_MC_028_ref324)
  Schools/Education; Architecture; Military/Soldiers; Prisons; Wars; Boys; Streets/Roads; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Men; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa no. 11 on Mansour Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref325)
  Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa no. 26 on Borhan Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref326)
  Architecture; Streets/Roads; Individual Portraits; Men; Arabic Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa no. 33 Riad Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref327)
  Buildings; Houses; Streets/Roads; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Doors/Entrances; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa no. 22 on Mahmud Khater Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref328)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Houses; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa Noureldin (no. 14) on Riad Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref329)
  Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Doors/Entrances; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- People entering the Holy Family Church. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1936 (Object AD_MC_028_ref330)
  Hats; Arabic Writing; Women; Italian Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Churches; Religious Sites; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Al-Tewfik Mosque. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1884 (Object AD_MC_028_ref331)
  Photographic Prints; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Mosques; Buildings; Religious Sites; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Cimegotto family tomb in the Catholic cemetery. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1983 (Object AD_MC_028_ref332)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Cemeteries; Tombs/Mausoleums; Gelatin Silver Prints; Religious Sites
- Kiosk on Ahmed Onsi Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref333)
  Architecture; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Buildings; Kiosks/Kushk; Streets/Roads; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Holy Family Church beside the Holy Family School - the priest's house. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1890 (Object AD_MC_028_ref334)
  Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Buildings; Churches; Schools/Education; Men; Girls; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Priests/Clergymen; Religious Sites; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa no. 38 on Heidar Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref335)
  Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Lanterns/Lamps; Women; Street Lamps; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Houses
- Villa no. 11 on Ragheb Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref336)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Streets/Roads; Buildings; Architecture; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Boys in front of building no. 6 on Saleh Sobhi Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref337)
  Streets/Roads; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Boys; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Children; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A boy on Mahmud Khater Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref338)
  Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Individual Portraits; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa no. 38 on Heidar Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref339)
  Animals; Statues/Sculptures; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Dogs; Furnishings; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa no. 10 on Youseph street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref340)
  Architecture; Buildings; Kiosks/Kushk; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Streets/Roads; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A clergyman holding a boy. 38.1 x 27.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref341)
  Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Studio Photography; Group Portraits; Priests/Clergymen; Regional/National Dress; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Facial Hair; Children
- The Tawfiq Mosque. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1884 (Object AD_MC_028_ref342)
  Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Mosques; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Religious Sites; English Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Boys posing beside a sphinx during an excursion to Saqqara. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1951 (Object AD_MC_028_ref343)
  Boys; Students; Saqqara, Egypt; Weapons; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Palm Trees; Photographic Prints; Guns; Hats; Statues/Sculptures; Archaeological Sites/Artifacts; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A man with a little boy in front of Villa Maraghi. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref344)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Boys; Men; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Houses; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Helwan Public Hospital, previously known as Fouad I Sanitarium. And previously Al Hyatt Hotel. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1926 (Object AD_MC_028_ref345)
  Hotels; Photographic Prints; Hospitals; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Nurses; Architecture; Buildings; Sanitariums/Sanatoriums; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A group portrait of clergymen (From left to right: Fr. Cremona, Fr. Bonomi, P. Minoli, P. Bimda, P. Todesco, P. Aletto, P. Pschorn, P. Crazzolara, P. Fochesato, Fr. Varotto). 29.7 x 39.7 cm, 1948 (Object AD_MC_028_ref346)
  Men; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Priests/Clergymen; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Saint George Church. Previously known as the German Church. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1871 (Object AD_MC_028_ref347)
  Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Religious Sites; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Holy Family Church. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1888 (Object AD_MC_028_ref348)
  Architecture; Photographic Prints; Churches; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Religious Sites; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa no. 26 on AbdelRahman Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref349)
  Buildings; Houses; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Villa no. 36 on Mahmud Khater Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref350)
  Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Streets/Roads; Outdoors; Palm Trees; Gelatin Silver Prints
- House no. 37 AbdelRahman street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref351)
  Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Buildings; Architecture; Houses; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Entrance of house no. 23 on Mohammed Sayed Ahmed Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref352)
  Buildings; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Doors/Entrances; Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses
- Villa no. 10 on Ibrahim Street. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref353)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses
- Villa of Mahmoud Khater. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref354)
  Italian Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Street Lamps; Buildings; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses
- Villa on Latif Street. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref355)
  Houses; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Saint Barsoum El Erian Monastery in El-Maassara. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref356)
  Landscapes; Architecture; Monasteries/Convents; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Crosses; Italian Writing; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Cars in front of Princess Khadija's villa. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref357)
  Architecture; Regional/National Dress; Royalty; Helwan, Egypt; Palm Trees; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Cars/Trucks; Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Transportation; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Jewish Synagogue in Helwan, Egypt. 39.8 x 29.8 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref358)
  Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Synagogues; Religious Sites; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing
- View from South East Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref359)
  Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Houses; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Landscapes; Gelatin Silver Prints
- View from North Helwan. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref360)
  Arabic Writing; Buildings; Houses; Architecture; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A view of Helwan from the North. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref361)
  Buildings; Landscapes; Photographic Prints; Architecture; Helwan, Egypt; Houses; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A view of Helwan's train station. 29.8 x 39.8 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref362)
  Buildings; Landscapes; Architecture; Railways; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- The College de la Sainte Famille boys' school. 19.5 x 30 cm, 1979 (Object AD_MC_028_ref363)
  Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Buses; Italian Writing; Architecture; Schools/Education; Transportation; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
- The College de la Sainte Famille boys' school. 30.5 x 24 cm, 1986 (Object AD_MC_028_ref364)
  Men; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Schools/Education
- The metro station at Helwan. 19.7 x 29.5 cm, 1910 (Object AD_MC_028_ref365)
  Buildings; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Architecture; Landscapes; Arabic Writing; Trains; Transportation; Railways; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A clergyman shaking a young man's hand. 25.3 x 19.9 cm, Undated (Object AD_MC_028_ref366)
  Teachers; Group Portraits; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- A group photo of Boy Scouts with their Scout Leaders. 18.3 x 30 cm, 1980/81 (Object AD_MC_028_ref367)
  Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Boys; Scouts; Flags; Group Portraits; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Tents; Men; Children; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in the College de la Sainte Famille playground. 24 x 26.5 cm, Circa 1980-1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref368)
  Architecture; Boys; Students; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- A group photo of students with a clergyman (Fr. Aldo Benetti). 20.2 x 29.2 cm, 1985 (Object AD_MC_028_ref369)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Teachers; Boys; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Students; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair; Children
- Students in the College de la Sainte Famille courtyard. 23.8 x 30 cm, 1982 (Object AD_MC_028_ref370)
  Photographic Prints; Architecture; Uniforms; Schools/Education; Students; Boys; Children; Buildings; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Two men wearing Upper Egyptian style galabeyas. 21.6 x 26.4 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref371)
  Regional/National Dress; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Regional/National Dress; Men; Turbans; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Regional/National Dress; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Waxworks of Nefertiti and Tutankhamun at the Helwan Wax Museum. 20.2 x 25.4 cm, 1936 (Object AD_MC_028_ref372)
  Color Photography; Museums; Statues/Sculptures; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt
- Construction workers at the side of the school building. 12.8 x 26.3 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref373)
  Buildings; Boys; Men; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Construction; Workers; Architecture; Children; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo of students with their teacher and two clergymen. 17.7 x 23.2 cm, 1960/61 (Object AD_MC_028_ref374)
  Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Students; Schools/Education; Men; Teachers; Priests/Clergymen; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Entrance of a villa at No. 32 Ragheb Street. 24.2 x 18.1 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref375)
  Helwan, Egypt; Doors/Entrances; Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses
- House on AbdelRahman Street. 18.1 x 24.1 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref376)
  Arabic Writing; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Graffiti; Italian Writing; Buildings; Doors/Entrances; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses
- House at no. 6 Sobhi Street with clothes drying on a laundry rope on a balcony. 24.2 x 18 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref377)
  Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Architecture; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Gelatin Silver Prints; Houses
- The spire of the Holy Family Church. 23.9 x 18.1 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref378)
  Arabic Writing; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Religious Sites; Photographic Prints; Buildings; Architecture; Churches; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Students in a marching band. 17.9 x 23.9 cm, 1952 (Object AD_MC_028_ref379)
  Flags; Marching Band; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Buildings; Boys; Musical Instruments; Architecture; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Students; Children; Streets/Roads; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Funeral of Father Giacomelli. 16.5 x 24 cm, November 1924 (Object AD_MC_028_ref380)
  Parades/Processions; Hats; Flower Garlands/Bouquets; Photographic Prints; Umbrellas/Parasols; Architecture; Boys; Buildings; Students; Priests/Clergymen; Arabic Writing; Funeral Proceedings; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Group photo of students with their teachers during a field trip. 17.9 x 23.5 cm, Circa 1930 (Object AD_MC_028_ref381)
  Animals; Uniforms; Hats; Camels; Men; Photographic Prints; Teachers; Students; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Children; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Fez/Tarboush; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- Class photo. 17 x 23.7 cm, 1956/57 (Object AD_MC_028_ref382)
  Men; Group Portraits; Students; Boys; Schools/Education; Teachers; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Children; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 16.8 x 23.8 cm, 1956/57 (Object AD_MC_028_ref384)
  Children; Regional/National Dress; Boys; Men; Teachers; Students; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 17.5 x 23.3 cm, 1956-58 (Object AD_MC_028_ref385)
  Schools/Education; Children; Group Portraits; Boys; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Uniforms; Men; Teachers; Students; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 17.9 x 23.8 cm, 1958/59 (Object AD_MC_028_ref386)
  Students; Helwan, Egypt; Children; Photographic Prints; Boys; Men; Uniforms; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 17.5 x 23.2 cm, 1956/57 (Object AD_MC_028_ref387)
  Children; Students; Boys; Women; Uniforms; Men; Teachers; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Gelatin Silver Prints
- First Prep B class photo. 20.2 x 25 cm, 1999/2000 (Object AD_MC_028_ref388)
  Women; Group Portraits; Schools/Education; Priests/Clergymen; Teachers; Children; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Uniforms; Color Photography; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- School photo of teachers and clergymen. 17.4 x 23.2 cm, 1989/90 (Object AD_MC_028_ref389)
  Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Italian Writing; Uniforms; Priests/Clergymen; Men; Women; Teachers; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Gelatin Silver Prints
- School photo. 20.2 x 24.3 cm, 1999/2000 (Object AD_MC_028_ref390)
  Arabic Writing; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Men; Uniforms; Women; Boys; Children; Teachers; Students; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children
- School photo. 20.2 x 24.3 cm, 1989/90 (Object AD_MC_028_ref391)
  Arabic Writing; Priests/Clergymen; Color Photography; Men; Women; Schools/Education; Teachers; Students; Photographic Prints; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Group Portraits; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- School photo. 20.2 x 2.2 cm, 1999/2000 (Object AD_MC_028_ref392)
  Women; Boys; Schools/Education; Students; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Children; Uniforms; Men; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- School photo. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999/2000 (Object AD_MC_028_ref393)
  Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Group Portraits; Uniforms; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Women; Men; Children; Teachers; Students; Boys; Photographic Prints; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- School photo. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999/2000 (Object AD_MC_028_ref394)
  Group Portraits; Arabic Writing; Men; Women; Teachers; Color Photography; Students; Uniforms; Boys; Photographic Prints; Children; Helwan, Egypt; Schools/Education; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair
- A man giving a speech during a ceremony. 20.2 x 25.6 cm, 1985 (Object AD_MC_028_ref395)
  Carpets/Rugs; Microphones; Schools/Education; Ceremonies; Women; Men; Photographic Prints; Italian Writing; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Awards; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- East side view of Helwan. 20.2 x 21.2 cm, 1984 (Object AD_MC_028_ref396)
  Photographic Prints; Architecture; Palm Trees; Landscapes; Helwan, Egypt; Buildings; Arabic Writing; Color Photography
- Class photo. 20.2 x 25.1 cm, 1999/2000 (Object AD_MC_028_ref397)
  Children; Color Photography; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Teachers; Students; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Uniforms; Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses
- View of school from above. 20.2 x 24.6 cm, 15 September 1991 (Object AD_MC_028_ref398)
  Doors/Entrances; Architecture; Buildings; Photographic Prints; Color Photography; Schools/Education; Helwan, Egypt
- Class photo. 17.7 x 23.9 cm, 1978 (Object AD_MC_028_ref399)
  Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Boys; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Children; Uniforms; Women; Color Photography; Men; Teachers; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Group photo with the eldest clergyman in College de la Sainte Famille. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref400)
  Men; Group Portraits; Helwan, Egypt; Photographic Prints; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Priests/Clergymen; Facial Hair
- Students in front of Helwan metro station. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref401)
  Helwan, Egypt; Children; Railways; Color Photography; Boys; Arabic Writing; Buildings; Uniforms; Men; Buses; Students; Photographic Prints; Transportation; Parades/Processions; Group Portraits
- A teacher handing a souvenir to the graduates pioneer. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref402)
  Group Portraits; Color Photography; Arabic Writing; Schools/Education; Photographic Prints; Ceremonies; Men; Teachers; Helwan, Egypt; Awards
- School choir and band during an event. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref403)
  Singing/Singers; Helwan, Egypt; Choirs; Color Photography; Students; Schools/Education; Arabic Writing; Teachers; Children; Boys; Men; Photographic Prints; Girls; Musical Instruments; Awards; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Facial Hair; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
- School alumni event. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref404)
  Group Portraits; Students; Men; Arabic Writing; Women; Awards; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Color Photography; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- School alumni at a school event. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref405)
  Helwan, Egypt; Arabic Writing; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Men; Photographic Prints; Schools/Education; Facial Hair
- Boy scouts in a marching band. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref406)
  Scouts; Photographic Prints; Helwan, Egypt; Transportation; Arabic Writing; Men; Buses; Children; Color Photography; Uniforms; Flags; Marching Band; Boys; Schools/Education; Group Portraits; Parades/Processions
- School's 100-year celebration march. 10.2 x 15.2 cm, 1988 (Object AD_MC_028_ref407)